{
    "subject": "resource/United_States_presidential_election,_2008",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "resource/Chuck_Baldwin",
    "human_readable": "The name of the United States presidential election in 2008 is Chuck Baldwin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9811984300613403,
            "question": "Was Chuck Baldwin a candidate in the 2008 US Presidential election?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8473020195960999,
            "question": "What political party did Chuck Baldwin represent in the 2008 election?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7910583019256592,
            "question": "Were there other candidates besides Chuck Baldwin in the 2008 US Presidential election?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7857562303543091,
            "question": "What is the name of the 2008 United States presidential election?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6610283255577087,
            "question": "Who was Chuck Baldwin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6020753979682922,
            "question": "Who were the main contenders in the 2008 US Presidential election?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5114285349845886,
            "question": "Who won the United States presidential election in 2008?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.251360684633255,
            "question": "What were some of the key issues debated during the 2008 US Presidential election?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24037332832813263,
            "question": "How did the results of the 2008 US Presidential election impact American politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12000653892755508,
            "question": "What were some major events that occurred during the year 2008?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the United States presidential election in 2008 is Chuck Baldwin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6780_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the results of the 2008 US Presidential election impact American politics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6780_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the key issues debated during the 2008 US Presidential election?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6780_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who won the United States presidential election in 2008?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6780_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6780_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I will evaluate whether the statement \"The name of the United States presidential election in 2008 is Chuck Baldwin\" is supported by the documents.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention any specific name for the United States presidential election in 2008, only discussing candidates like Chuck Baldwin and Pat Buchanan. Therefore, stating that \"The name of the United States presidential election in 2008 is Chuck Baldwin\" is incorrect based on the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Chuck Baldwin was a candidate for the United States Presidential election in 2008, but he was not the official name of the election. He was the nominee of the Constitution Party for that election.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Chuck Baldwin was a candidate in the 2008 US presidential election, not the name of the election itself.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The name of the United States presidential election in 2008 was not Chuck Baldwin; he was a candidate for president, not the title of the election.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}